good afternoon hello you blogger
добрый день привет вы блогер
don’t
не
go recognized you like the
ходите признана вам лайк
first one I meet which flag
первые которую я встречаю которого флаг
blessed weighs well done he didn’t buy
блаженный весит молодец он был не купил
wet
влажной
not just
не просто
hang wider varna lads don’t know
вешают шире варны хлопцы не знаю
correctly said
правильно сказал неправильно
hot as lazy as a meadow but
горячо как поленитесь как поляницу но я
I don’t own 7 buried such shiro
не владею 7 закопано таких shiro сиро
rent  I’m a blogger, yes, I’m collecting the
аренда уж я блогер да я вот собираем
opinion of Russians, alas, not in Ukraine, so
мнение россиян увы не в украине вот вы
let’s store it, then I’ll make you happy,
давай на его хранение то я вас обрадую
smear exhale, we apply an opinion, it’s understandable,
мажьте выдыхать наносим мнение понятно
yes, we are together this opinion, this opinion is
да мы вместе это мнение это мнение
officially called this on
официально у вас это называется
purpose, no, it’s called all
специально нет это называется во всем
over the world because it’s  is called there is a concept of
мире так как это называется есть понятия
war
войны
legal war is officially declared
юридическая война официально объявлен
sort of like I understand look if you are not
вроде как я понял смотрите если вы не
already a goat dear blogger tell me the answer to the
уже коза уважаемый блогер скажите мне на
question the war is officially declared
вопрос ответ война официально объявлен
no no russia
нет нет россии
polishing
полировки
if you like you and physical
если вы как у вас и физическое
education I have just it and less
образование у меня как раз она и менее
super here is me  also there is a Vedic
супер вот меня тоже есть ведической
let's if you say that it is so
давайте если вы говорите что так есть
show me some document according to the
покажите мне какой-то документ согласно
cat  sometimes you don’t consider the war to be
которого вы на иногда война не считать
legal, it’s like that, otherwise let’s
нормативно-правовых это так а то давайте
read the document and read that the ball
документ он и читаете что шаровой
is to determine such a document it is the
является определить такой документ он
specific name of the document it records
конкретное название документа он записи
on the organization’s website there are a lot of
на сайт организация там очень много
documents to help a lot of documents to the
документов помочь много документов
search engine
поисковике
war for you look at you all kinds of how
война для смотрите вы вам все виды как
lawyer so if you
юрист так если вы
say tell me in which document
утверждать скажите мне в каком документе
poke my nose take it now God
тыкните мне нос возьмите сейчас богом
open it wrong you
открой не так вы
name the document with a horse Ukrainian main
назовите документ с лошадь украинец main
agar we are used to you that
agar мы ты привык что тебе все должны
everyone owes you all are obliged to look at the reprimand for whose
все обязаны смотрите выговор за чей
stone the water is not here you look r go
камень вода не вот вы смотрите г перейти
to which  -some UN document and sisi yourself on the
в каком-то документе оон и сиси сам на
site you learn to find the
сайте учишь найти
previous one,
предыдущий
look let me click
смотрите давайте я щелкаю
on I work for a
по работаю на
lawyer I saw who work for free
юриста видел который бесплатно работать
let's you look I'm only probably in
давайте вы смотрите я только наверно в
Ukraine the story is just that you are assembling
украине история только что вы сборища
how right we think that in Ukraine you
как правильно мы считаю что в украине вы
think that there is in Ukraine
считаете что на украине есть
let's look at the site, it doesn't have a
давайте так я посмотрел на сайте он нету
document that talks to itself
документа который разговаривает сам с
merge  here are all these
сливаетесь вот все эти
Russian such
российские такие
Ukraine fobs, yes, it’s the way he
украина фобы да именно путем он
wakes up that the labels are Ukrainian, you
просыпается метки украинец ты там
tell her there and then, yes, that is, if
расскажи ней-то и дальше да то есть если
you are a lawyer and a lawyer’s account, then let’s say not a
ты юрист и счет юрист то давай скажу не
specific document, so you can
конкретный документ так еще можете
open such and such a convention with such a
открыть такую то там конвенции такой
[ __ ] on the site he  she is dancing, the
сукой на сайте он она есть танцы , б
lawyer said even shorter under the laws
юрист сказал еще короче под вы законы
given by many on google and so I
дал стве многие по google и так вот
searched there higher than in the civil
искал там повыше чем в цивильном у
code of the vitarna pumped by the criminal
кодекс витарна прокачанном криминальному
you absolutely look like a Wessex bulldozer
вами абсолютно вид балды уэссекса
says so no documents he may
говорит так никаких документов он мая
there wonderful you meaning still wine
там чудных вы значение еще вина
is expressed there  the length is also on the hair and
выражается там длиною еще и на волосы и
what we say is the product of the cops he is so
что мы говорим продукт менты он так то
he took a big pen and the concept of
он взяли большую перу и понятием
aggression how she is guilty on the projects
агрессии как она вины по проектам
convinced if it was a long creation of him
convinced если было долго твор него так
so he feasts to understand mobile all i
у него пируют понять мобильные all i
wanna and not hotly
wanna и не горячо
let's say the dina is violated by guilt before
скажем дина нарушается виною до этого
a single hair om ye
единого волосы ом йе
in taverns of discounts
в трактирах скидок
side teeth fit attack and 1 but
стороны зубы вяжется нападат и 1 но
london without by the looks of his father and from auto
лондон без по видам его отца и от авто
russia
россия
I’ll just destroy and the authorities of
как раз и порушу и власти
thoughts  it’s saints,
думалось святые
but who didn’t give a contract, a dispute is possible
но кто не давал ни договора спор можно и
on the ios network of a crochet of containers, so you and the
на ios сети накида тары так вот вам и
protective news before ukraine covered them
защитная новости до украины накрыл их
while dipping your cheek specifically show the two
макаешь пока щеку конкретно покажи двоих
that you are suffering that such documents
что ты страдаешь что такие документы это
will show the kahneman and nose I you know so we
покажет канеман и носом я вы знаю так мы
will be cool  to istanbul it’s scarlet,
будут крутые to istanbul это алая
let’s say they are pe-2 years old and happy right and right, and
скажем их года пе-2 рады прямо и мастя и
we mine our denunciation of this our information
мы моем донос этой нашу информацию беша
besha and that’s about the axis both in ukraine and in the
и бишь около оси как в украине так и в
retinue, including in the russian
свите в том числе и в российской
federation, there’s no slave to forget where
федерации нет раба забывать еще там где
even don’t let your brother  and
даже брату не дайте и
Ukrainianophobes Olga for Datura not
украинофобов ольге за дурмана не
propaganda, I also we will be there, it was the
пропаганду я также мы там будем было
Donbass, we were hanging in the lesson, then later we are
донбасс висим уроке мы тогда потом мы
guilty against you and we also deal with them
повинны противо ты и на них тоже
subscribe to the channel and
занимаемся подписывайтесь на канал и
sites
сайты комментарии пидпысуйтесь